<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stremio News</title>
    <link>https://blog.stremio.com/category/stremio-news/</link>
    <description>Latest news and updates from the Stremio Blog</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 02:05:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #67 – Stremio Lite for iOS/MacOS Updated</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-67-stremio-lite-for-ios-macos-updated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We updated the Stremio Lite app for iOS and MacOS. Here’s what changed: Added Trakt login button Updated KSPlayer version Fixed Trakt events not being sent iOS specific: update app icon Retain previously selected TV show season Added subtitle styling settings Fixed trash bin icon on settings page for long Stremio server urls Changed the…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 08:53:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-67-stremio-lite-for-ios-macos-updated/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/stremio-tech-update-cat-4.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio 2D Released to Meta Quest!</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-2d-released-to-meta-quest/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While we already released “Stremio VR” for Meta Quest back in April 2025, out of popular demand we also released “Stremio 2D” now for Meta Quest and it’s now available in the Meta Horizon Store! This is a windowed app that can be used for multi-tasking on the Meta Quest device. Here are some screenshots…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 08:40:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-2d-released-to-meta-quest/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/2d-MQ.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #66 – Stremio Lite for Apple TV (tvOS) Updated</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-66-stremio-lite-for-apple-tv-tvos-updated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We updated the Stremio Lite app AppleTV (tvOS). Here’s what changed: Added Trakt login button Updated KSPlayer version Fixed Trakt events not being sent Added webp image decoding on older tvOS Retain previously selected TV show season Added subtitle styling settings Changed the style of TV show episodes to conform to our current design Added…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 15:42:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-66-stremio-lite-for-apple-tv-tvos-updated/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/tvOS-release.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio VR Released to Pico VR Devices</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-vr-released-to-pico-vr-devices/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We just released our Stremio VR app worldwide (with the exception of China) to the Pico Content Store. Our VR app should now be visible on the following devices: Pico 4 Ultra Pico 4 Pro Pico 4 Pico Neo3 (all future Pico devices) We have also released the “Stremio 2D” app, our android mobile windowed…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:40:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-vr-released-to-pico-vr-devices/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/VR-pico.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #65 – Stremio 5 Update for MacOS and Stremio 5 Release for Windows ARM</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-65-stremio-5-update-for-macos-and-stremio-5-release-for-windows-arm/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We updated the Stremio v5 app for MacOS with the following changes: new dock icon allow the screen saver during video pause We also release Stremio v5 for Windows ARM! If you want to download Stremio v5 for Windows ARM devices, you can do so from this link until the cache expires. We may or…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:44:56 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-65-stremio-5-update-for-macos-and-stremio-5-release-for-windows-arm/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/stremio-tech-update-cat-1.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #64 – Stremio Android TV Updated</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-64-stremio-android-tv-updated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We updated the Stremio Android TV app (v1.8.1) to fix an issue with some Android vendors where users could not log in or see posters, but instead would see an error saying “Failed to create cache directory for temporary files” As we have changed the cache directory to solve this issue, all users would need…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:51:26 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-64-stremio-android-tv-updated/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/stremio-tech-update-blur-8.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio is Now Available on Fire OS Store!</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-is-now-available-on-fire-os-store/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[After removing the “Stremio” scam app from Amazon Store recently due to trademark infringement, you can now find the official Stremio app on FireOS devices in the Amazon App Store! Stremio no longer needs to be sideloaded on any FireOS device anymore and it includes automated updates. Stay tuned as we may still have more…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 16:54:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-is-now-available-on-fire-os-store/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/stremio-tech-update-cat-5.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Lite Released for TVs with Vidaa OS! (Hisense, Toshiba, Sharp, etc)</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-lite-released-for-tvs-with-vidaa-os-hisense-toshiba-sharp-etc/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stremio Lite is now available for TVs running Vidaa OS, this includes brands such as Hisense, Toshiba, Sharp, AKAI, etc. This is a global release and there is no minimum model year for TVs running Vidaa, as long as you have the latest OS updates, you should be able to find the app in the…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 10:51:28 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-lite-released-for-tvs-with-vidaa-os-hisense-toshiba-sharp-etc/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/hisense-tv-release.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #63 – Stremio VR Updated</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-63-stremio-vr-updated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We just updated the Stremio VR app for Meta Quest devices. Here’s what changed: Fixed an issue where the streams list would not load Fixed the order of addons (to be the same as install order) Fixed an issue where the app could freeze when opening a metadata page Fixed an issue with the HDR…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 15:31:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-63-stremio-vr-updated/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/stremio-tech-update-cat-2.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #62 – Stremio Lite for MacOS Release</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-62-stremio-lite-for-macos-release/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Stremio Lite now supports MacOS as a native app and can be installed from the MacOS App Store. It supports Apple native features such as Handoff and movie/tv show artwork in Control Center. Unlike the iOS app running on macOS, it supports Intel processors also, proper UI size, hiding cursor when playing a video and…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 12:41:38 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-62-stremio-lite-for-macos-release/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/stremio-tech-update-blur-8.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
