<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stremio News</title>
    <link>https://blog.stremio.com/category/stremio-news/</link>
    <description>Latest news and updates from the Stremio Blog</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 01:46:41 GMT</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #44 – Stremio v5, Web & VR Updated</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-44-stremio-v5-web-vr-updated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We just released a new version of Stremio v5 for Windows, a new version of Stremio VR and updated Stremio Web, let’s see what changed! Stremio v5 shell: Fixed an issue with skipping multiple episodes when using the “next video” button while binge watching Fixed other binge watching specific issues Stremio Web (which is also…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 12:19:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-44-stremio-v5-web-vr-updated/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Adobe_Express_20230922_1439320_1.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #43 – Stremio v5 and Stremio Web Updated</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-43-stremio-v5-and-stremio-web-updated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We just released a new version of Stremio v5 for Windows, and updated Stremio Web, let’s see what changed! Stremio v5 shell: Fixed an issue that would show the volume bar as disabled in some cases Stremio Web (which is also the UI for Stremio v5): Fixed non latin characters font issue Fixed font weight…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 15:34:25 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-43-stremio-v5-and-stremio-web-updated/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2024/01/Tech-update-for-Stremio-web.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #42 – Stremio VR Updated</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-42-stremio-vr-updated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We updated the Stremio VR app for Meta Quest devices. Let’s see what changed: Improved UI for Meta Quest 2 Improved Video Quality Added Episode Progress and Check mark on Watched Fixed Subtitle Cues Getting Stuck When Hiding the Video Control Panel Added Recentering on Y/B buttons Added Next Episode Button for Series on Video Control…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 11:45:41 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-42-stremio-vr-updated/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Adobe_Express_20230922_1439320_1.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Stremio on Hisense TV with Vidaa OS</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/installing-stremio-on-hisense-tv/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Some Hisense TVs (specifically from USA) use Android TV instead of Vidaa OS, on those TVs you can install Stremio directly from the Play Store. Note: If you are a developer and would prefer to run this project locally instead of following the steps in this article, you can find it on GitHub here While…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:18:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/installing-stremio-on-hisense-tv/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/hisense-tv-release.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio VR Hotfix</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-vr-hotfix/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We released a hotfix for the new Meta Quest app to resolve an issue where the app could crash when opening the streams page for some users. Other minor changes were also included, such as fixing an overlapping issue in the seasons selector and removing the Unity splash screen. Happy watching!]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 15:02:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-vr-hotfix/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/hotfix-2.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio VR Released for Meta Quest Devices</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-vr-released-for-meta-quest-devices/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Introducing Stremio in VR! You can install it on your Meta Quest 3, 3S, 2 or Pro device from the Horizon Store by searching for “stremio”. The Stremio VR app also supports new video types that no other Stremio app supports: all VR video types: 180, 190, 200, 220 and 360 degree all 3D video…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 17:01:20 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-vr-released-for-meta-quest-devices/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/meta-quest-release.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #41 – Stremio v5 and Stremio Web Updated</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-41-stremio-v5-and-stremio-web-updated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We just released a new version of Stremio v5 for Windows, and updated Stremio Web, let’s see what changed! Stremio v5 shell: More IPC events for window state (full screen, window restored) Fix opening external links Stremio Web (which is also the UI for Stremio v5): Player: add pause on window minimize setting (shell only)…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 14:18:16 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-41-stremio-v5-and-stremio-web-updated/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/09/Adobe_Express_20230922_1439320_1.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Stremio AI</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/introducing-stremio-ai/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We’re excited to unveil Stremio AI! Harnessing advanced artificial intelligence to tackle a fundamental challenge: distilling movie and episode plots into concise, accessible summaries. Stremio AI watches content for you, allowing you to reclaim valuable time for meaningful connections with loved ones rather than spending hours viewing everything yourself. Our AI creates comprehensive summaries of…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 08:37:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/introducing-stremio-ai/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/stremio_ai_2.jpg" length="10000" type="image/jpeg" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio is now available on Philips TVs with TitanOS (models 2024+)</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-is-now-available-on-philips-tvs-with-titanos-models-2024/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[While Stremio has been available on Philips TVs running Android TV for a long time now, today we released Stremio for TitanOS! TitanOS is the new TV operating system running on 2024+ Philips TV models. The Stremio app for Philips TV is still new and due to limitations of this new OS it is currently…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 15:29:34 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-is-now-available-on-philips-tvs-with-titanos-models-2024/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/03/philips-tv-release.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio v5 Playback Hotfix</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-v5-playback-hotfix/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[A few hours ago users created bug reports regarding playback issues with the latest Stremio v5 update, we reverted the changes 1 hour ago while we could investigate the issues further. We have now deployed a hotfix for the bug, if you are encountering any playback issues with Stremio v5 on Windows you should use…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 22:31:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-v5-playback-hotfix/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/hotfix-2.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
