<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Stremio News</title>
    <link>https://blog.stremio.com/category/stremio-news/</link>
    <description>Latest news and updates from the Stremio Blog</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 01:46:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>

    <item>
      <title>Stremio Mega Update! Stremio v5 for MacOS, Usenet & Archive Streaming, Like & Loved Buttons and More!</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-mega-update-stremio-v5-for-macos-usenet-archive-streaming-like-loved-buttons-and-more/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[Good news, everyone! Today we have a huge update! So big in fact that we are splitting it into numerous blog posts. Pick your destiny: Stremio v5 MacOS Release! (with ARM support) and Stremio Lite TestFlight for MacOS: https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-v5-macos-release!-(with-arm-support)/ Stremio New Streaming Sources (Usenet, FTP, RAR, ZIP, 7ZIP, TGZ, TAR): https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-new-stream-sources-usenet-rar-zip-ftp-and-more/ Stremio Liked and Loved…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:38:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-mega-update-stremio-v5-for-macos-usenet-archive-streaming-like-loved-buttons-and-more/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/mega-update.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio New Stream Sources (Usenet, RAR, ZIP, FTP and more)</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-new-stream-sources-usenet-rar-zip-ftp-and-more/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[At Stremio we pride ourselves in working with streaming (as the name suggests), so today we present to you MANY new streaming capabilities. As of right now these have only been implemented in Stremio v5 for desktop with plans on gradually releasing it to other platforms too. Note: All these new streaming capabilities are still…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:37:03 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-new-stream-sources-usenet-rar-zip-ftp-and-more/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/usenet.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Like and Love Buttons</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-like-and-love-buttons/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We’ve been adding like and love buttons for some time in our apps. We’ve been waiting for these buttons to be implemented in more platforms before we release them, and today is the day! While we have many more plans for these new features, as of now you can install the “Stremio Liked” and “Stremio…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:36:48 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-like-and-love-buttons/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/like-or-love.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Android TV and Android Mobile Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-android-tv-and-android-mobile-update/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We released a minor update for Android TV (v1.8.0) and Android Mobile (v2.1.4) today, let’s see what changed! Android TV:– Added foreground service to fix issue with the external player torrent playback– Various small UI changes Android Mobile:– Fixed an issue with some deeplinks crashing the app– Fixed an issue with opening addons manifests This…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:36:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-android-tv-and-android-mobile-update/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/stremio-tech-update-blur-8.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio v5 / Web Updated</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-v5-web-updated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We just updated Stremio Web (which includes the UI for Stremio v5 too), here’s what changed: Added translatable error messages on the Intro page Player: Add support for media play/pause keys MetaPreview: hide ActionButton label on mobile Player: Add media session support Calendar: Poster visibility improvements App: Add shortcuts modal Settings: Add player video mode…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:36:13 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-v5-web-updated/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/stremio-tech-update-cat-5.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio v5 MacOS Release! (with ARM support)</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-v5-macos-release-with-arm-support/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We just released Stremio v5 for MacOS with separate ARM and Intel support! We have been working on this for a very long time… and it’s finally here! You can download it now from our downloads page. (use this link to bypass caching until it expires) In a strange twist of events, we also released…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 17:35:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-v5-macos-release-with-arm-support/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/macOS-release-2.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #59 – Android Mobile Update and tvOS TestFlight</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-59-android-mobile-update-and-tvos-beta/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We released a new version of the android mobile app (v2.1.1) Let’s see what changed: Fixed crash when opening One Pace addon Added support to open .torrent files Added support to open addon manifest from the search bar Added support to open magnet link from the search bar Added guest login Added setting for exprimental…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 15:26:32 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-59-android-mobile-update-and-tvos-beta/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/stremio-tech-update-cat-2.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #58 – Stremio VR Updated</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-58-stremio-vr-updated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We made a huge update to the Stremio VR app! Let’s see what changed: Added HAND TRACKING support Added ROOM SCALE support Added SCREEN RESIZING features Redesigned video control panel Added streaming progress indicator Fixed issues with trailers and YouTube playback Fixed duplicate video tags on the movie info page Fixed issue where videos sometimes…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:32:31 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-58-stremio-vr-updated/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/stremio-tech-update-cat-4.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Tech Update #57 – Apple TV (tvOS), Android TV and Android Mobile Apps Updated</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-57-apple-tv-tvos-android-tv-and-android-mobile-apps-updated/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We just released new versions of the Apple TV (tvOS), Android TV and Android mobile apps. Apple TV changes: fixed playback of live videos added external player support for Infuse fixed embedded subtitles showing even when disabled from settings fixed adding to library from dropdown menu fixes navigation bug where focus would get locked to…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 08:14:29 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-tech-update-57-apple-tv-tvos-android-tv-and-android-mobile-apps-updated/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/stremio-tech-update-cat-1.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stremio Lite for Apple TV (tvOS) is Now in App Store</title>
      <link>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-lite-for-apple-tv-tvos-is-now-in-app-store/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[We just released the highly anticipated Stremio Lite for Apple TV (tvOS), you can install it at this App Store link. As this is our first release for this device, please send any bug reports to this link. Some screenshots of the app: It make take an hour or two for the app to show…]]></description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 20:18:46 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://blog.stremio.com/stremio-lite-for-apple-tv-tvos-is-now-in-app-store/</guid>
      <enclosure url="https://blog.stremio.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/tvOS-release.png" length="10000" type="image/png" />
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
